<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>pulsifer.ca</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on pulsifer.ca</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Curriculum Vitae</title><link>/cv/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cv/</guid><description>Summary 👋 Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Jonathan Pulsifer, a security engineer who fits into the Staff Engineer Tech Lead &amp;amp; Architect archetypes. I enjoy working with Google Cloud Platform, Kubernetes, and Containers. Some might call me a sysadmin, some might call me a DevOps engineer, but I just like computers 🧑‍💻
Employment History Shopify, 2016-2021 Staff Infrastructure Security Engineer I spent the majority of my time at Shopify on the Infrastructure Security team, where I was the engineering lead.</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>Greetings. I&amp;rsquo;m @jonpulsifer, welcome to my personal website &amp;ndash; I built it myself! 😂
For my last $dayjob, I was a Staff Security Engineer working on Kubernetes 💙 at Shopify.
✋ I am open for employment! If you&amp;rsquo;d like to hire me, please email jonathan@pulsifer.ca
PGP: 0x0472D3B3F5012430</description></item><item><title>Compliant Infrastrucure as Code</title><link>/talks/compliant-infrastructure-as-code/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/talks/compliant-infrastructure-as-code/</guid><description>This is a talk I gave at Cloud and AI DevFest Montreal 2019</description></item><item><title>Keyless Entry: Securely Access GCP Services from Kubernetes</title><link>/talks/keyless-entry-workload-identity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/talks/keyless-entry-workload-identity/</guid><description>This is a talk I gave with Aaron Small and Mike Danese about foregoing long lived credentials (PKI) for short lived access tokens on GKE.
You can read about it over on the Google Cloud Blog, too!
No more exporting Google service account keys or lumping permissions onto one account. Kubernetes now provides a way for Kubernetes workloads to prove their identity outside of their cluster. We’ve built on this to deliver a simpler, more secure way to authenticate to Google services whether you’re running Kubernetes on GKE, GCP, on-premises, or a hybrid mix.</description></item><item><title>Securing the Software Supply Chain</title><link>/talks/secure-software-supply-chain-binauthz/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/talks/secure-software-supply-chain-binauthz/</guid><description>This is a talk Jianing Guo and I gave at Google Cloud Next 2018 about securing software supply chains with Binary Authorization. I showed off the tool my team developed called Voucher which we later donated to the Grafeas organization.
I also wrote about this over on shopify.engineering.
Containers have revolutionized how we develop, package, and deploy applications. As enterprises create more containerized workloads, the security of the software supply chain must be top of mind.</description></item><item><title>Securing Shopify's PaaS on GKE</title><link>/talks/securing-the-paas/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/talks/securing-the-paas/</guid><description>This is a talk I gave at SecTor, as well as at KubeCon the following month!
Shopify has leveraged Kubernetes through Google Container Engine (GKE) to build its new cloud platform. This PaaS is currently serving the majority of the company&amp;rsquo;s internal tools as well as business-critical production workloads. Moving to Kubernetes and a public cloud is no easy task, especially for a security team.
Unfortunately for us, a hosted solution does not offer all the features we&amp;rsquo;ve come to love in Kubernetes including NetworkPolicies, PodSecurityPolicies, and admission controllers among others.</description></item><item><title>Infrastructure Security 2.0</title><link>/talks/infrastructure-security-2-0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/talks/infrastructure-security-2-0/</guid><description>Shopify has leveraged Kubernetes through Google Container Engine (GKE) to build its new cloud platform. This PaaS is currently serving the majority of the company&amp;rsquo;s internal tools as well as business-critical production workloads. Moving to Kubernetes and a public cloud is no easy task, especially for a security team.
Given industry&amp;rsquo;s limited experience with cloud computing and cloud native technologies, this talk hopes to demystify some of these core cloud concepts.</description></item><item><title>CEVO Client Information Disclosure</title><link>/posts/cevo-information-disclosure/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/cevo-information-disclosure/</guid><description>tl;dr CEVO was a global eSports company built around North America’s largest competitive online PC gaming league. The CEVO client is software that is mandatory to be run during online play. The client was transmitting user authentication details (usernames and passwords) and private conversations in clear text which made them susceptible to eavesdropping attacks.
Good day CS:GO friends!
Reference: /r/globaloffensive post about ESEA&amp;rsquo;s password security from early spring 2015.</description></item><item><title>Archive</title><link>/archive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/archive/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>